streetsmash.com 2013-06-19

# Privacy Policy - Streetsmash

[Home](http://streetsmash.com/)  »  Privacy Policy

What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey.

When registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your: name and e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

1\. To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

2\. To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

3\. To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your requests and inquiries.)  
The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent.

How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.
